gethifi.com 2012-05-08

# Privacy Policy - GetHiFi

### Join our **HiFi mailing list** to receive the latest news & updates

Last Modified:  November 29, 2010

**Privacy Policy**

HiFi (a division of New Media Technology Group Corporation) is committed to respecting the privacy of all persons using the gethifi.com web site and associated services (the **“Site”** ).  This Privacy Policy describes the information gathering and dissemination practices for the Site.  It does not apply to information collected by us off-line.

**_Collection and Use of Personal Information_**

When you establish your HiFi account or purchase other services through our Site, you must provide us with your personal information, including as applicable your name, e-mail address, and physical address. 

If you are set up to pay by credit card, then HiFi or its payment processor will collect personally identifiable information (credit card number, billing address, phone number) and keep this information on file in our secure server in order to process your recurring invoices. This information is only used to verify credit card authenticity, and issue invoices as per your agreement with HiFi. Upon discontinuation of your service, your credit card information will be deleted.  If we are unable to process your subscription, this information, along with your account information, may be used to contact you.

We may collect and analyze information about your use of the Site in order to determine your compliance with the HiFi Terms of Use.  We may also collect and analyze such information for statistical purposes. This information may be analyzed and/or aggregated to determine appropriate modifications and enhancements to the Site.

HiFi uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our service. Your IP address is used with the IP addresses of other members to gather broad demographic information.

We or our business partners may use “cookies” in connection with the Site.  Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site places on an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purpose and/or to enhance a user’s experience. You may adjust your computer to disallow the storing of cookies. However, certain aspects of our Site may not function properly if cookies are disabled. We are not responsible for the use of cookies by other Web sites that are accessed through us.

**_Use and Disclosure of Information_**

**_ _** HiFi will use the personal information you provide to provide requested services, alert you of new products and services, features and enhancements, respond to your support issues, and/or notify you of upgrade opportunities, promotions, and special offers.     You agree that we may communicate with you via email and any similar technology for any purpose relating to the Site.

We may also:

  * Disclose your personal information to companies who work for HiFi to provide a product or service to you that you have requested or to process payments. Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personal information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.
  * Release personal information and/or other information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state, federal or international laws or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant. 
  * Disclose personal information and/or other information about you that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our agreements, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend against any third-party claims, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of the Site, and protect the rights, property, or personal safety of HiFi, our users or others. 

**_Children_**

**_ _** HiFi does not knowingly allow children under the age of eighteen (18) to sign up for an account on the Site or to otherwise disclose any of their personal information to us.   If you are under 18 years old, please do not use or access our Site.  We do not intend to collect information about children under the age of 18.  If we later obtain actual knowledge that a user is under 18 years of age, we will take steps to remove that user’s information from our systems. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under 18 whom you believe has disclosed personal information to us, please contact us at info@gethifi.com so that we may delete and remove the child’s information from our systems.

**_Opt-Out_**

**_ _** We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving certain communications from us and our business partners, at the point in the registration process where we request information about you.  In addition, all marketing e-mails from HiFi will provide you with the opportunity to unsubscribe from future marketing mailings.  Even if you opt out of such mailings, however, we reserve the right to send you e-mail and other communications to disclose maintenance and other service-related issues.

**_Access to Account_**

**_ _** Please contact us at [info@gethifi.com](mailto:info@gethifi.com) if you need to update and/or correct your account information.   You may need to supply certain information so that we can try to verify that you have authority to modify this information.

**_Third-Party Sites_**

**_ _** The Site may contain links to other Internet sites. We have no responsibility for the privacy practices of other Web sites, including the web sites of our business partners. Whenever a web browser window is opened in HiFi that does not show a web page created by HiFi (noted by a HiFi copyright statement at the bottom of such pages), then it should be assumed that HiFi privacy policies do not apply. 

**_Legal Requirements; Sale of Business_**

**_ _** We intend to protect your privacy to the fullest extent possible as described in this policy while also fulfilling our responsibility to uphold all applicable laws and regulations. Due to potential legal requirements and other possible circumstances, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed or accessed in ways not otherwise described in this policy. We may be compelled under law to disclose information to government or third parties under certain circumstances or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Further, we can, and you hereby authorize us to, disclose any information to law enforcement or other government officials that we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in compliance with the law.

In the event that all or part of HiFi is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, you agree that we may transfer or assign the information we have collected from you as part of such merger, acquisition, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

**_United States_**

**__**The Site is hosted in the United States. If you are accessing the Site from outside the United States, please be advised that through your continued use of the Site, which is governed by U.S. law and this Privacy Policy, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

**_Security Measures_**

We have implemented reasonable security measures on the Site to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the personal information under our control. Additionally, HiFi takes reasonable steps to ensure that our third party business partners, including our hosting partners, provide sufficient protection for personal information.

**_Terms of Use_**

**__**This Privacy Policy is part of and incorporated into HiFi Terms of Use, which includes provisions such as limitations on damages, dispute resolution, and application of North Carolina USA state law.

**_Modifications_**

**__**This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically by HiFi, as reflected by the "last modified" date above. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes.  Material amendments to this Privacy Policy shall be communicated to you at the time you log into the Site, by e-mail, or by notice here.  Your continued use of the Site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions.

We intend to provide the Site and related services that are beneficial to you and that you trust. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or the information handling practices of the Site, please contact us at info@gethifi.com.

## Latest on Twitter

@lukestokes Our datacenter, Softlayer had a ~10 minute network issue that affected some parts of the country, HiFi itself was uninterrupted.
